Abraham Perez

Victorville, California, United States

abedevelops@gmail.com | (909) 636-2637 | github.com/AbeofSpade | linkedin.com/in/abraham-perez-aa7a3b9b

SUMMARY

As a Full-Stack Developer, I have a passion for creating innovative solutions that improve the lives of others. I am currently pursuing & building on the skill set I've learned in Software Engineering through Codecademy, Mimo & Scrimba, which I hold certifications in Full-Stack Development. I am always eager to learn new skills and technologies, and I am committed to using my expertise to make a positive impact on the world.

SKILLS

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Python, SQL, MySQL, PostgreSQL, React, Node.JS, TypeScript, Swift, Git, Leadership, Goal setting

WORK EXPERIENCE

OCTLC, Inc./Sustain Recovery

Nov 2017 - Mar 2024

Lead Recovery Coach

- I worked with adolescents struggling with mental health and/or drug addictions.
- Helped provide support as they dig deeper into traumas or family issues after having sessions with a therapist.
- Helped the clients learn life skills and create structure in their lives to that they become habits they can take home when they graduate.
- Helped and show the clients how to have fun sober and present them to a community of life minded people through a 12 step program.

Vemma Jan 2013 - Sep 2016

Independent Distributor

- I spearheaded the promotion of health products and business opportunities at Vemma, leading to improved customer well-being and financial status. I excelled in recruiting and training a team of distributors, fostering leadership development through effective training methods and leading by example.
- Successfully promoted health products and business opportunities
- · Recruited and trained a team of distributors
- Emphasized leadership development through training and setting a positive example

Nordstrom Jan 2015 - Jan 2016

Picker

- Efficiently located and retrieved merchandise in the pick mod for orders at Nordstrom.com.
- Ensured timely preparation of orders for packers to meet shipping deadlines.
- Maintained a high level of accuracy and attention to detail in order fulfillment processes.

EDUCATION

CodeAcademy Nov 2023 - Nov 2024

Full-Stack Developer

Mimo Nov 2023 - Jul 2024

Python Developer

Scrimba

Front-End Developer

CERTIFICATIONS

Full-Stack Developer

Python Developer